<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<configuration>
   <page name="action">
	    <width>529</width>
	    <height>350</height>
	    <video></video>
	    <content>
	        <![CDATA[
	        <p align='center'><font size="16"><b>Welcome to the Data Warehouse</b></font></p>
	        <p>InfoAlameda hosts a wide array of data pertaining to Alameda County. To help you make use of it all, we have arranged the data and tools in a (hopefully) logical fashion.</p>
			<textformat blockindent="4">	    
	        <p><b>1. </b>To begin viewing and mapping data, you can select <b>'Create a Map'</b>- this will take you to the next screen to pick your first category.</p>
	        <p><b>2. </b>If you have already made your first map above and you want to get creative and explore other data in combination, you can <b>'Add a Second Layer'</b>. Again, you get to narrow your options with a category on the next screen.</p>
	        <p><b>3. </b>If you don't want a map, but prefer to build an interactive chart/graph of your data, select <b>'Make a Chart'</b>.</p> 
	    	</textformat>
	    	<p>As you move through the data selection process, click the help icon <img src='assets/images/i_help.png' /> to get informatin specific to the step you are on.</p>
	    	]]>
	    </content>
	    <btnlabel>Click to continue</btnlabel>
	</page>
	<page name="category">
	    <width>529</width>
	    <height>250</height>
	    <video></video>
	    <content>
	        <![CDATA[
	        <textformat indent="20">
	        <p align='center'>
	            <font size="16"><b> Pick a category</b></font>
	        </p>
	        <p>
	          To help you find what you are searching for in our database we've grouped all the data into these categories.
	          The details give you an indication of just what data variables are available within each category.
	        </p>
	        <p>Simply Click on the box of the category that interests you.</p>
	        <p><b>Remember</b>: The ribbon of buttons above only lets you navigate backwards, so if you do not select an option on this page
	        but rather hit the 'Pick a Subcategory' button, the tool will not let you select a subcategory.</p>
	     	 </textformat>
	       ]]>
	    </content>
	    <btnlabel>Click to continue</btnlabel>
	</page>
	<page name="subcategory">
	    <width>529</width>
	    <height>250</height>
	    <video></video>
	    <content>
	        <![CDATA[
	        <textformat indent="20">
	        <p align='center'>
	            <font size="16"><b> Pick a subcategory</b></font>
	        </p>
	        <p>Within each of our categories there are subcategories- these represent a more sensible grouping of the data elements. Here you can norrow down your field of interest to a specific disease type, economic condition or sub-population</p>
	        <p>Simply Click on the box of the subcategory that interests you.</p>
	        <p><b>Remember</b>: The ribbon of buttons above only lets you navigate backwards, so if you do not select an option on this page
	        but rather hit the 'Pick a Subcategory' button, the tool will not let you select a subcategory.</p>
	        </textformat>
	     ]]>
	    </content>
	    <btnlabel>Click to continue</btnlabel>
	</page>
	<page name="variable">
	    <width>529</width>
	    <height>250</height>
	    <video></video>
	    <content>
	        <![CDATA[
	        <textformat indent="20">
	        <p align='center'>
	            <font size="16"><b> Pick a variable category</b></font>
	        </p>
	        <p><b>1. </b>To begin selecting your data click on the folder that fits your interest-sometimes there will only be one- just select the single folder in that case</p>
	        <p><b>2. </b>Clicking the folder will open a tree of data variables available</p>
	        <p><b>3. </b>Now you can choose a variable - click on the item</p>
	        <p><b>4. </b>Since many of the variables are available for different geographies and years, you must select from the table the exact specs of the variable you want</p>
	        <p><b>5. </b>When everything is selected, the blue <font color="0x0000ff">'Dispay the Data'</font> button will be active. Click this button to map or chart what you selected.</p>
	       </textformat>
	       <img src='assets/images/choose2.jpg'/>
	       ]]>
	    </content>
	    <btnlabel>Click to continue</btnlabel>
	</page>
	
</configuration>
